https://www.biggunexhaust.com/cookie-policy-us/

EXO STAINLESS
EXO Stainless is the most durable exhaust in our lineup. Constructed of high-strength 304 stainless steel from front to back, EXO Stainless is sure to withstand even the most brutal of riding conditions and use. Using our existing
EXO
EXO Series came about from a realization of the need for a bigger and better muffler that could handle the huge demands of the larger, more powerful sport ATV motors. The EXO Series is our ground up approach at just that. A unique hexagon…
EVO U
With its deep and throaty tone, the EVO U series surely doesn’t disappoint. Designed specifically for utility ATV’s, sport utility ATV’s and Side x Sides, the EVO U series is not for the faint of heart when it comes to raw power …
EVO R
The EVO R series draws on our rich heritage of making power. Offered for various off road MX and sport ATV models, the EVO R is a tried-and-true series that will save weight, add noticeable performance gains and sound tremendously …
EVO S
Race-proven power is what you get with an EVO S series exhaust. If a performance-driven, quality-made exhaust system is what you are after, look no further. Our EVO S series is offered for a variety of sport bike and scooter…
EVO M
Our EVO M series has been a Big Gun staple for over a decade. Though there have been slight changes and improvements over the years the goal has always been to produce noticeable performance gains. We can’t forget to mention …
ECO
The ECO series is for the price-conscious rider that wants to get every ounce of power out of his/her motor but does not want to break the bank. Offered as only slip ons, the ECO series is affordable yet powerful. A cheap …
WARHEAD
GP-inspired, quality-made and affordably-priced; all terms that describe the Warhead. This slip on tip is designed to replace your existing muffler and add style, increase sound and save weight. The Warhead is available …
TFI POWER BOX
When installing an aftermarket exhaust, proper tuning is a must. The Big Gun Power Box is a plug-and-play fuel controller that allows you to properly tune your fuel injected motorcycle, ATV or Side x Side …
REV BOX
If you are looking to swap out your stock CDI box, the Big Gun Rev Box is an affordable alternative to highly-priced OEM replacement boxes. It increases the overall RPM limit over the stock box and advances the timing curve …
GEAR
Show off your Big Gun love away from your bike, ATV or Side x Side with our gear lineup. Pick up some shirts, hats, stickers or even a one of a kind trailer hitch cover for your truck.
PARTS
Freshen up your Big Gun exhaust with our extensive replacement parts and accessories offerings. From new exhaust stickers, to springs, spark arrestors and quiet inserts, we’ve got you covered.
INFO
NEWS
TECH TALK
PROPER TUNNING FAQ
POWER BOX 101
DEALERS
CONTACT US
VEHICLE SELECTOR:
Type
Vehicle
ATVMXSide x SideStreet
Vehicle:
Make
Make:
Model
Model:
Year
PARTS
This page was last changed on January 23, 2020, last checked on January 23, 2020 and applies to citizens of the United States. 1. IntroductionOur website, https://www.biggunexhaust.com (hereinafter: “the website”) uses cookies and other related technologies (for convenience all technologies are referred to as “cookies”). Cookies are also placed by third parties we have engaged. In the document below we inform you about the use of cookies on our website.2. What are cookies?A cookie is a small simple file that is sent along with pages of this website and stored by your browser on the hard drive of your computer or another device. The information stored therein may be returned to our servers or to the servers of the relevant third parties during a subsequent visit.3. What are scripts?A script is a piece of program code that is used to make our website function properly and interactively. This code is executed on our server or on your device.4. What is a web beacon?A web beacon (or a pixel tag) is a small, invisible piece of text or image on a website that is used to monitor traffic on a website. In order to do this, various data about you is stored using web beacons.5. ConsentWhen you visit our website for the first time, we will show you a pop-up with an explanation about cookies. You do have the right to opt-out and to object against the further use of non-functional cookies.5.1 Manage your consent settingsYou can also disable the use of cookies via your browser, but please note that our website may no longer work properly.6. Cookies6.1 Technical or functional cookiesSome cookies ensure that certain parts of the website work properly and that your user preferences remain known. By placing functional cookies, we make it easier for you to visit our website. This way, you do not need to repeatedly enter the same information when visiting our website and, for example, the items remain in your shopping cart until you have paid. We may place these cookies without your consent.6.2 Social media buttonsOn our website we have included buttons for Facebook and Instagram to promote webpages (e.g. “like”, “pin”) or share (e.g. “tweet”) on social networks like Facebook and Instagram. These buttons work using pieces of code coming from Facebook and Instagram themselves. This code places cookies. These social media buttons also can store and process certain information, so a personalized advertisement can be shown to you.Please read the privacy statement of these social networks (which can change regularly) to read what they do with your (personal) data which they process using these cookies. The data that is retrieved is anonymized as much as possible. Facebook and Instagram are located in the United States.7. Placed cookiesGoogle Analytics
We use Google Analytics for website statistics.
Name
Retention
Function
Statistics (anonymous)
_ga
2 years
Store a unique user ID
_gid
1 day
Count and track pageviews
_gat
1 minute
Filter requests from bots
Sharing
For more information, please read the Google Analytics Privacy Policy.Facebook
We use Facebook for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons.
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
_fbp
3 months
Track visits across websites
actppresence
Sharing
For more information, please read the Facebook Privacy Policy.Automattic
We use Automattic for website development.
Name
Retention
Function
Statistics
tk_ai
session
Store a unique user ID
Sharing
For more information, please read the Automattic Privacy Policy.Cookie Notice for GDPR
We use Cookie Notice for GDPR for cookie consent management.
Name
Retention
Function
Functional
cookie_notice_accepted
persistent
Checks if cookies can be placed
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.WooCommerce
We use WooCommerce for webshop management.
Name
Retention
Function
Functional
wc_cart_hash_*
session
Store items in shopping cart
wc_fragments_*
persistent
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.Google Fonts
We use Google Fonts for display of webfonts.
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
Google Fonts API
none
Request user IP address
Sharing
For more information, please read the Google Fonts Privacy Policy.YouTube
We use YouTube for video display.
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
GPS
session
Store location data
Functional
Sharing
For more information, please read the YouTube Privacy Policy.Miscellaneous
Name
Retention
Function
Purpose pending investigation
SGPBSubscription*
ab_tests_features
complianz_policy_id
365 days
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.8. Your rights with respect to personal dataYou have the following rights with respect to your personal data:
you may submit a request for access to the data we process about you;
you may object to the processing;
you may request an overview, in a commonly used format, of the data we process about you;
you may request correction or deletion of the data if it is incorrect or not or no longer relevant, or to ask to restrict the processing of the data.
To exercise these rights, please contact us. Please refer to the contact details at the bottom of this cookie statement. If you have a complaint about how we handle your data, we would like to hear from you.9. Enabling/disabling and deleting cookiesYou can use your internet browser to automatically or manually delete cookies. You can also specify that certain cookies may not be placed. Another option is to change the settings of your internet browser so that you receive a message each time a cookie is placed. For more information about these options, please refer to the instructions in the Help section of your browser.10. Selling data to third partiesWe do not sell data to third parties11. Contact detailsFor questions and/or comments about our cookie policy and this statement, please contact us by using the following contact details:Big Gun Exhaust Inc.
190 Business Center Drive, Suite B
Corona, CA 92880
United States
Website: https://www.biggunexhaust.com
Email: sales@biggunexhaust.com
Phone number: 714-970-0423This cookie policy was synchronized with cookiedatabase.org on January 2, 2020
OUTLANDER 400 (Non EFI)
OUTLANDER MAX 400 (Non EFI)
SCRAMBLER XP 850 H.O.
Why is Proper Tuning a Must?
Cookie Policy (US)
Copyright © 2018 Big Gun Exhaust
